

## Profile

Experience as a system administrator for over 4 years.

Solid knowledge of how modern computer systems work, extensive Linux and network administration experience, a sound understanding of Computer Science concepts, and plenty of enthusiasm for bringing DevOps and SRE practices into reality.

I'm glad find mates with passionate about their work, and add my knowledge to they a common cause.

# Employment History

MRI Service Specialist at Medical Institute named after Berezin Sergey (MIBS), Ryazan'

November 2017 — October 2020

- Maintenance and repair, if necessary, of the Siemens Magnetom Symphony 1.5T magnetic resonance imager with auxiliary equipment;
- Installation and maintenance of specialized software;
- Maintenance and improvement local network from 100mbps to 1gbps;
- Administration Windows Server 2012 (DICOM/SQL servers) and Linux (deb based distro).

## System Engineer at EPAM, Ryazan'

October 2020 — June 2022

- Created and implemented service for collect information from dozens of environments about the versions of a particular service and its status.
- Designing Serverless AWS architecture for application biotech/cheminformatics from MVP to production release
- Led a small DevOps/System Engineer team using Kanban to support several RnD projects in crop protection domain
- Implemented and configured logging, monitoring, and alerting on several k8s clusters using Grafana and Loki
- Supported several projects and their environments single-handedly
- Automating CI/CD routine procedures
- Provisioning various AWS infrastructure services using IaC methods, working with customer support team

## Senior Site Reliability Engineer at VK, Moscow

June 2022 — Present

 Support and development VK Cloud Solution product based on OpenStack technology

### **Details**

Ryazan'

+79537436903

vlad.kamerdinerov@yandex.ru

Date of birth

24/06/1995

### Links

Linkedin GitHub

### **Skills**

Git

**Ansible** 

**Jenkins** 

Docker

**Kubernetes** 

**AWS** 

Linux

OpenStack

### **Hobbies**

Cars, surf skating

• Adapted a cloud solution product on ARM architecture

# Education

# Bachelor, Ryazan State Radiotechnical University, Ryazan'

September 2013 — June 2017

Radio engineering systems for location, navigation and television

# Master, Ryazan State Radiotechnical University, Ryazan'

September 2017 — June 2019

Wireless technologies in communication systems

## Courses

## **EPAM University Program, EPAM**

August 2020 — October 2020